starthealthystayhealthy.in 2011-11-19

# Nestle Start Healthy Stay Healthy

“Nestlé” and ”Nestlé Group” in this Privacy Policy refer to Nestlé S.A. and any of its affiliated companies as appropriate to the context. 

“Third Parties” for the purposes of this Privacy Policy means any company other than Nestlé S.A. and its affiliated companies. 

At this website, we only collect personal information that YOU want to provide to Nestlé or that is needed to provide to and improve Nestlé’s service to you. We collect direct personal information such as name, telephone number and e-mail address as well as indirect information such as “cookies” or connection or system information or the settings you have on your web browser. We however do not actively seek to identify any individual visitor, with the exception of investigating security breaches or cooperating with authorities pursuant to a legal matter. 

“Cookies” is a tiny element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive so we can recognize you when you return. 

Your personal information will be used only for the purposes for which you provided it to Nestlé. It will also be used to administer, support and obtain feedback on the level of our services and to prevent breaches of security, the law or our contract terms. 

Nestlé takes all necessary measures to keep your personal information private and secure. Only authorised Nestlé Group staff, Third Party (Non Nestlé Group) companies (i.e. service providers) staff or our business partners' authorised staff (who have contractually agreed to keep all information secure) have access to your personal information. To ensure your personal information is protected, Nestlé maintains a secure IT environment and has the appropriate measures in place to prevent unauthorised access (i.e. hacking). 

Nestlé links to other websites to offer you an opportunity to review connected and interesting information related to Nestlé. These Third Party (non Nestlé Group) websites are outside of our control and are not covered by this Privacy Notice. If you access other websites using the links provided, the operators of these websites may collect your personal information. Please ensure that you are satisfied with the Privacy Policies of these Third Party websites before you submit any personal information. Nestlé tries, as far as we can, to ensure that all non-Nestlé linked websites have equivalent measures for protection of your personal information, but we cannot be held responsible legally or otherwise for the activities, privacy policies or levels of privacy compliance of these Third Parties. 

Nestle may change this Privacy Policy, change, modify or withdraw access to this website, and/or the content of these pages at any time without notice. 

This Agreement is governed by the laws of the Republic of India. This Agreement is deemed to have been signed and executed in New Delhi, India and you expressly submit yourself to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Indian Laws and the Courts in New Delhi, India only, in respect of any disputes arising in any manner out of or relating to this site. You expressly waive any objection of whatsoever nature to Indian jurisdiction and agree not to raise any objection or take any plea as to Indian jurisdiction on the ground of forum inconvenient, delay, expense, hardship or otherwise howsoever.
